

CONTACT

- +639619820348
- bernardolandley@outlook.com
- Baguio City, Philippines
- linkedin.com/in/landleyber nardo

EDUCATION

2022-2023 ASIAN INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT

 Dado Banatao-Startup Incubator Program

2018-2021 SAINT LOUIS UNIVERSITY

- Masters in Information Technology
- DOST STRAND Scholar

2013-2017 SAINT LOUIS UNIVERSITY

- BS in Computer Science
- Consistent Dean's Lister

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JS
- PHP, Zend Framework/Laminas, Laravel
- Python
- Java
- Tailwind, Bootstrap
- Livewire, React, Vue.js
- MySQL, Redis
- Digital Ocean, Laravel Forge, AWS, MS Azure

LANDLEY BERNARDO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Experienced Co-Founder with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Technical Support, Management, Team Leadership, SQL, and Customer Service. Strong business development professional with a Master's degree focused in Information Technology from Saint Louis University (PH).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Straive

2023 - PRESENT

Senior Software Engineer

- Develop and maintain a UI and API applications.
- · Perform server maintenance.
- Support machine learning tasks.

WeR Solutions

2022 - 2022

Front-end web developer

- Convert the designs into an HTML page with its CSS and JS.
- Develop UI components to interface with backend API endpoints.

The PMO Co.

2018 - 2022

Co-founder/CTO

- In charge of technical development from planning and design to implementation and deployment.
- Maintain strong relationships with partners, agencies, and vendors to support marketing initiatives.

REFERENCE

Pamela Tecson

Sophie Sales

The PMO Co. / CEO

WeR Solutions / COO

Phone: 09167799750

Phone: 09068554982